(Leonard:)-I'm not going out tonight, Raj.
-All right.
(Raj:)Would you mind if I went to your room
and downloaded Asian pornography?
(Leonard:)Very much.
(Raj:)Doesn't have to be Asian.
(Leonard:)-Don't worry. You'll meet a girl.
-No, I won't.
(Leonard:)Yes, you will.
And she'll be beautiful...
(Leonard:)...and kind and sexy and funny and
everything you ever wanted in a woman.
(Raj:)-You really think so?
-I do.
(Leonard:)You'll fall hopelessly in love
and give her your heart.
(Leonard:)She'll take it and grind it
into pathetic little pieces.
We will have sex first, right?
(Sheldon:)Mm, mm, mm.
That's Italian.
So was Leonard okay
with you coming over?
(Sheldon:)Oh. Yes.
In fact, he said, "I'm fine. I don't care."